let questions = [
    {
        numb:1,
        question : "A person sold a stove for Rs. 423 and incurred a loss of 6%. At what price would it be sold so as to earn a profit of 8%?",
        answer : "Rs. 486",
        options :[
            "Rs. 887",
            "Rs. 482",
            "Rs. 586",
            "Rs. 486"     
       ]
    },
    {
        numb:2,
        question : "A sells a car to B at 10% loss. If B sells it for Rs. 54000 and gains 20%, the cost price of the car for A was..",
        answer : "Rs. 50000",
        options :[
            "Rs. 45000",
            "Rs. 50000",
            "Rs. 54500",
            "Rs. 56000"     
       ]
    },
    {
        numb:3,
        question : "Ramesh sold a statue for a price 25% higher than the original price of the statue. He had however bought the statue at 20% discount on the original price. With the profit of Rs. 2025, find the original price of the statue.",
        answer : "Rs. 4500",
        options :[
            "Rs. 4500",
            "Rs. 4320",
            "Rs. 5244",
            "Rs. 5000"     
       ]
    },
    {
        numb:4,
        question : "Two bicycles were sold for Rs. 3990 each, gaining 5% on one and losing 5% on the other. The gain or loss percent on the whole transaction is",
        answer : "0.25% loss",
        options :[
            "2.5% loss",
            "2.5% gain",
            "0.25% loss",
            "None of The Above"     
       ]
    },
    {
        numb:5,
        question : " A shopkeeper earns a profit of 15% after selling a book at 20% discount on the printed price. The ratio of the cost price and printed price of the book is?",
        answer : "16:23",
        options :[
            "16:23",
            "12:47",
            "16:28",
            "12:23"     
       ]
    },
    {
        numb:6,
        question : "Simran bought pet food worth Rs. 56000. She then sold 1/3rd of it incurring a loss of 40%. What profit she must earn on rest of the supplies to nullify this loss?",
        answer : "20%",
        options :[
            "40%",
            "35%",
            "22%",
            "20%"     
       ]
    },
    {
        numb:7,
        question : "Suman buys 160 chocolates for Rs. 480. She wanted to earn 30% profit by selling them. But Rakesh visited her and she gave him 25% of those chocolates at the cost price itself. But even after doing this, she earned a profit of 30% as decided. For how much did she sell each chocolate?",
        answer : "Rs. 4.2",
        options :[
            "Rs. 3.8",
            "Rs. 4.2",
            "Rs. 10",
            "Rs. 5.6"     
       ]
    },
    {
        numb:8,
        question : "Uma wants to gain 15% profit on her sale of sugar. She buys 120 kg of sugar at Rs. 24 per kg to mix with 180 kg of sugar bought at Rs. 28 per kg. She sells the sugar mix at â€¦.",
        answer : "Rs. 9108",
        options :[
            "Rs. 9108",
            "Rs. 5268",
            "Rs. 5364",
            "Rs. 2254"     
       ]
    },
    {
        numb:9,
        question : " A sold a car to B at a profit of 25%. B incurred loss of 15% while selling the same car to C. A spent Rs. 50000 for this car. At what price did C buy it?",
        answer : "Rs. 53125",
        options :[
            "Rs. 55845",
            "Rs. 82545",
            "Rs. 53125",
            "Rs. 80000"     
       ]
    },
    {
        numb:10,
        question : "A boy pays Rs. 369 for an article marked at Rs. 600, by enjoying two successive discounts. If the first discount is of 25%, how much should be the second discount?",
        answer : "18 %",
        options :[
            "12 %",
            "44 %",
            "28 %",
            "18 %"     
       ]
    },
   
]
